voicesnet.org 2012-06-08

# Poetry and Poems

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, age, e-mail address, City, State and Country of origin. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables them to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

**_To personalize your experience_** (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 

**_To improve our website_** (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 

**_To improve customer service_** (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 

_**To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature**_

**_To send periodic emails_**

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: Each member can decide in their user profile whether to be included on our site mailing list or not, which determines whether one receives emails like newsletters and response notifications. Emails for fan notifications can be turned on or off separately in your user profile. 

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. We offer the use of secure servers for any ordering that occurs. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

Google, through their advertising network, uses cookies through our site to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that they can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy**

Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at Terms and Conditions. 

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on February 11th, 2010
